<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Abhiyantriki</string>
    <string name="clg_name">K. J. Somaiya College of Engineering</string>
    <string name="Open">Opens navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="Close">Closes navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="kjsce">The K. J. Somaiya College of Engineering was established in 1983
        at Somaiya, Vidyavihar.It offers 4-year bachelors degree courses in five diverse
        departments.KJSCE is an Autonomous college affiliated to the University of Mumbai and
        is recognized by the All India Council for Technical Education.The college hosts three huge
        festivals: Abhiyantriki, Skream, and Symphony.</string>
    <string name="abhiyantriki">Abhiyantriki is the annual technical festival of K.J. Somaiya
        College of Engineering. Previously, organizations like DRDO, BARC, ISRO, DAE have
        participated in the fest along with prominent personalities such as the late Dr. A.P.J.
        Abdul Kalam, R Chidambaram, Abhas Mitra etc. It is a culmination of the brightest young
        minds coming in to compete in the various technical activities that take place during the
        two day long celebration.</string>
    <string name="year_98">Abhiyantriki introduced as an individual, standalone festival of technical
        grandeur and pomp.</string>
    <string name="year_08">Funds collected this year were all donated for the rehabilitation of the
        flood struck Bihar and Abhiyantriki rose in popularity with extensive media coverage.</string>
    <string name="year_09">KJSCE marks 25 years since its inauguration, and the closing ceremony of
        Abhiyantriki was ornamented by the presence of late Dr. A.P.J. Abdul Kalam</string>
    <string name="year_14">The maiden year for Start-up and Auto Expo, Abhiyantriki this year also
        encompassed Rohit Suri, the Jaguar India CEO as one of the keynote speakers</string>
    <string name="year_16">Abhiyantriki extended by a day, now was a two-day long fest with its
        flagship event being a technical exhibition presided over by ISRO.</string>
    <string name="year_17">Attending to the likes of DRDO, DAE and BARC, Abhiyantriki garnered a
        running footfall of over 15,000 for the first time in its history!</string>

</resources>
