<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Abhiyantriki 2019</string>
    <string name="clg_name">K. J. Somaiya College of Engineering</string>
    <string name="Open">Opens navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="Close">Closes navigation drawer</string>

    <!-- For Home Activity -->
    <string name="kjsce">The K. J. Somaiya College of Engineering was established in 1983 at
        Somaiya, Vidyavihar. It offers 4-year bachelors degree courses in five diverse departments.
        KJSCE is an Autonomous college affiliated to the University of Mumbai and is recognized by
        the All India Council for Technical Education. The college hosts three huge festivals:
        Abhiyantriki, Skream, and Symphony</string>
    <string name="abhiyantriki">Abhiyantriki is the annual technical festival of K.J. Somaiya College
        of Engineering. Previously, organizations like DRDO, BARC, ISRO, DAE have participated in
        the fest along with prominent personalities such as the late Dr. A.P.J. Abdul Kalam, R
        Chidambaram, Abhas Mitra etc. It is a culmination of the brightest young minds coming in to
        compete in the various technical activities that take place during the two day long
        celebration.</string>

    <!--  For Timeline -->
    <string name="year_98">Abhiyantriki introduced as an individual, standalone festival of technical
    grandeur and pomp.</string>
    <string name="year_08">Funds collected this year were all donated for the rehabilitation of the
        flood struck Bihar and Abhiyantriki rose in popularity with extensive media coverage.</string>
    <string name="year_09">KJSCE marks 25 years since its inauguration, and the closing ceremony of
        Abhiyantriki was ornamented by the presence of late Dr. A.P.J. Abdul Kalam.</string>
    <string name="year_14">The maiden year for Start-up and Auto Expo, Abhiyantriki this year also
        encompassed Rohit Suri, the Jaguar India CEO as one of the keynote speakers.</string>
    <string name="year_16">Abhiyantriki extended by a day, now was a two-day long fest with its
        flagship event being a technical exhibition presided over by ISRO.</string>
    <string name="year_17">Attending to the likes of DRDO, DAE and BARC, \nAbhiyantriki garnered a
        running footfall of over 15,000 for the first time in its history!</string>

    <!-- For Events Cards -->

    <string name="pubg">The PUBG fever has infected everyone and with a game as addictive and
        intense as this, it’d be a shame for it to not be a part of Abhiyantriki ‘18. It’s time to
        loot all the crates in sight and face the terrors of Pochinki as you run away from the
        dreaded blue circle of death.</string>
    <string name="laser">Abhiyantriki is not all about fascinating gizmos. There’s something in the
        bag for everyone. Increase the fun quotient with Laser Tag only at KJSCE Abhiyantriki 2018.
        Come and engage in this challenging battle of lasers to get the experience of a lifetime.
    </string>
    <string name="drone">Do drones remind you of surveillance and all things boring? Take part in
        the drone racing event organised by Drona Aviation only at Abhiyantriki 2018 and that too
        at no cost!</string>
    <string name="meme">Memes have become a part and parcel of a student’s life. And for engineers,
        memes are a stress buster during exams. An early morning cup of tea with some amusing memes
        to go through makes one’s day lively. And Abhiyantriki 2018 has something exhilarating for
        all those meme fanatics out there. The best entries will win amazing prizes. Don’t miss this
        chance to show everyone who’s the greatest meme-lord of KJSCE.</string>
    <string name="fifa">Popularized as a part of the Indian pop culture because of the shenanigans by
        AIB in association with Shahrukh Khan, we present to you FIFA Manager. Be in charge of a team
        and pave its way towards victory. Have you got what it takes to manage a team and lead it to
        victory?</string>
    <string name="cs">From time immemorial, one thing that describes engineers the best would be the
        legendary FPS, Counter Strike. It’s time to Rush B and come out of your congested, damp and
        clammy hostel rooms and go guns blazing in a tournament to decide who has got the eagle eyed
        vision worthy of the Golden Glock.</string>
    <string name="CastleMath">With the lectures frying your brains to a crisp with the arrays of
        Epsilons and Gammas, it is time to bring math outside the classroom. With this exciting event
        presented by Team Emfinity, we hope all the zealots of math bring out their inner fangirl.
    </string>
    <string name="digitalposter">To those who thought Abhiyantriki is only for the tech-heads,
        coders, and the occasional \'pro\' gamers, here\’s a one-off contest, exploring the
        technicalities of art, the Poster Design Competition! In this contest, participants have to
        make a poster (digitally designed), recreating some of their favourite Indian war movie
        posters! Best entries will be printed out and presented to the Indian Army at Abhiyantriki
        2018.</string>

    <string name="kjscemumbai">To find a solution, think outside the box. To solve a cube think
        inside of the box. To compete with cubes as your weapons, observe the sides, memorize the
        algorithms and spot the glitches. Abhiyantriki and Cubenama are here with a Pre-Event for
        the avid cubers, so get ready to compete and delve into a different dimension of the cubes.
    </string>
    <string name="tpp">Have a great idea? Construct a well drafted ‘Technical Paper’ on a topic/
        theme given below in the link. Hope to see you in Abhiyantriki 2018!</string>
    <string name="technovate">Formulation of engineering solutions to the underlying issues
        hindering the smooth functioning of various aspects of the society. Hope to see you in
        Abhiyantriki 2018!</string>
    <string name="techquiz">A questionnaire to test your technical knowledge and rack your brains to
        its optimum potential. Hope to see you in Abhiyantriki 2018!</string>
    <string name="techhunt">A classic game of follow the clues but with a element of surprise,
        where your technical knowledge will be tested to its limits. Hope to see you in Abhiyantriki
        2018!</string>
    <string name="zeroeb">This event will require a culmination of your creativity and technical
        skills to create a self sufficient building wherein each and every minute detail will be
        well thought out to increase efficiency and renewability. Hope to see you in Abhiyantriki
        2018!</string>
    <string name="defeatingthemishaps">Formulate feasible engineering solutions to help reduce the
        number of accidents and efficiently provide help in case of unavoidable calamities, taking
        the current transportation scenario into consideration.</string>
    <string name="reversingtheglobalwarming">Come up with innovative engineering solutions to reduce
        the deep decarbonisation of our society from all possible pollution sources (cooking, air
        conditioning, etc.) to reverse the global warming.</string>


    <!-- For Ideate Fragment-->
    <string name="ideate">Ideate is one of the very core events of Abhiyantriki where participants
        from various colleges bring out the best of ideas focusing on a problem statement to engineer
        feasible and efficient technology.</string>

    <!-- For Events Tabs-->
    <string name="tab_text_1">Technicals</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Ideate</string>
    <string name="tab_text_3">Informals</string>
    <string name="tab_text_4">Shield</string>
    <string name="tab_text_5">Pre-Events</string>

    <!-- For Tech Expo Fragment -->
    <string name="techExpo">A display of the most innovative technology from around the country,
        ranging from high-speed drones to drag-and-drop robot arms, the Tech Expo is the most
        eye-catching event of Abhiyantriki. Having collaborated with big names like DRDO, BARC,
        ISRO, DAE and many more, the tech expo will surely ignite the fire of science and
        engineering in your budding mind!</string>
    <string name="indianArmy">With the motto \‘Service before Self\' the Indian Army is one of the
        world’s most powerful armed forces. And in synergy with Abhiyantriki, the impossible becomes
        a reality. Technology only observed in works of fiction become a reality here, as the Indian
        Army brings in their best, from weapons seen in an Arnold Schwarzenegger movie to firepower
        unheard of!</string>

    <!-- For Auto Expo Fragment -->
    <string name="autoexpo">Auto Expo is one of the star attractions of Abhiyantriki ever since its
        starting years. It has collaborated with major companies like Jaguar, Audi, Fiat, Mercedes
        Benz etc. This event helped students to gain perspective about different cars, their
        specifications, and the enhancements in the technology involved and is a one-stop
        destination for all the automobile enthusiasts out there.</string>

    <!-- For Internship Expo Fragment -->
    <string name="internship">The primary aim of this expo is to help the desiring candidates to get
        internship opportunities in renowned companies. It was started in Abhiyantriki 2015 and
        since then, has been providing a lot of students the internship they deserve in a variety of
        fields ranging from marketing to IT. These internships are bound to give a boost to their
        career.</string>

    <!-- For Expos Tabs -->
    <string name="tab_text_6">Tech Expo</string>
    <string name="tab_text_7">Auto Expo</string>
    <string name="tab_text_8">Internship Expo</string>

    <!-- For Speaker Section -->
    <string name="speaker">With sessions conducted by skilled experts of diverse fields, the Speaker
        Sessions held during Abhiyantriki are bound to leave you in awe. Abhiyantriki so far has
        seen speakers such as Mr. Hetal Kotak, CEO of Lee Cooper, Mrs. Saloni Suri, PR Consultant of
        Rolex Institute and Asia Society, Dr. Abhas Mitra, and R. Chidambaram, former director of
        BARC.</string>


    <!--  Parvaah Strings         -->
    <string name="parvaahTitle">
        The social initiative of K.J. Somaiya College of engineering, named Parvaah, works each year
        with a purpose of providing to the underprivileged and oppressed.
        This time around, Parvaah is on a mission to establish a “Zero Waste Community,” wherein constant
        efforts are being made for reducing, reusing and recycling the waste generated and contributing back to the society.
    </string>
    <string name="parvaahSchoolAwareness">
        It is said ‘The students of today are the future of tomorrow’. Realising this, Parvaah plans on visiting schools in Mumbai and teach the students the basic principles of a zero waste community. It’s an attempt to educate the students as well as the staff of the school about the need to go zero waste. Along with this, we also aim at transforming the schools into a zero waste locality. Instilling a sense of responsibility in the students towards managing their waste will go a long way in realising our goal of a cleaner Mumbai.
    </string>
    <string name="parvaahPlasticECollectionDrive">
    Keeping in mind the perils caused by plastic and e-waste, Parvaah has decided to conduct a collection drive for these hazardous items. The plastic and e-waste which is collected will then be sent for recycling thus ensuring there is no harm caused towards the environment. E-waste contains heavy metals like cadmium, lead, copper, and chromium that can contaminate the environment while plastic, on the other hand, is made from toxic compounds known to cause illness, and because it is meant for durability, it is not biodegradable. Constituting a major chunk of our waste, a proper and efficient disposal of these items is the need of the hour.    </string>
    <string name="parvaahGanpatiVisarjanCleanup">
    The festive season of Ganesh Chaturthi is one which is celebrated with great pride and enthusiasm all across the state. But what follows at the end of 11 days is a beach replete of floral waste and half-broken idols. To overcome this, Parvaah has decided to organize a beach clean-up at the Girgaum Chowpatty on the day after Ganesh Visarjan to clear up the beach of all its waste. We plan on associating with other college students from that area and make this a ground-breaking youth moment. Similarly, we would also be spreading awareness about celebrating an eco-friendly Ganesh Utsav in the weeks leading to the festival.
    </string>
    <string name="parvaahSignalShala">
    Signal Shala is an innovative concept initialized by Samarth Bharat Vyaspith along with Thane Municipal Corporation, to provide education to underprivileged children living on signals in Thane. Situated in a small container below a bridge, the main aim of Signal Shala is to make these kids capable of adjusting themselves with the mainstream world. We at Parvaah plan on spreading awareness about Zero Waste with the help of these kids and also teach them simple ways to treat their waste. As signals witness a frequent number of vehicles, we aim to use this medium to make the people aware of the basic habits they can follow to effectively manage their waste. We at Parvaah believe that only when it is a collective effort of all its citizens can a city truly make great progress in achieving a goal.
    </string>
    <string name="parvaahSecretSanta">
    On the occasion of Christmas, Parvaah plans on visiting an orphanage and celebrate with the kids. To further the joy, we would also be distributing toys, goodies, and sweets among the kids. This would be followed by playing games with the children, interacting with them and ensuring that everyone has a smile on his or her face.
    </string>
    <string name="parvaah_Marathon">
    Parvaah plans to organize a marathon to raise awareness about waste crisis. The marathon is proposed to take place in the Ghatkopar area of suburban Mumbai. We would also be starting a fundraiser event through this marathon.
    </string>

    <!--     About Abhiyantriki         -->
    <string name="address">K. J. Somaiya College of Engineering \nVidyanagar, Vidya Vihar East, Ghatkopar East, Mumbai, Maharashtra 400077 </string>


    <!--        getInvolved String      -->
    <string name="getInvolved1">Do you know someone with the potential to build something that pawns over the technology being displayed in Abhiyantriki and will leave the audience awestruck? If yes, feel free to add their details in the form below and we’ll reach out to them!</string>
    <string name="getInvolved2">Sponsors and Partners are a key component that helps make Abhiyantriki a fest worthy of all the praise and acclaim it has been garnered over the ages. Along with monetary support, you can feel free to help us out in any other way possible. Fill out the form below to get in touch with us :</string>
    <string name="title_activity_nav1">NavActivity1</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>

    <!-- For Speakers Activity  -->
    <string name="speaker1">Dr. S. Christopher is the former Chairman of DRDO (Defence Research and
        Development Organisation). He is largely credited for pioneering India\'s first indigenous
        AEW&amp;C (airborne early warning and control) system. Mr. Christopher obtained his BE (Hons)
        in Electronics &amp; Communication Engineering from University of Madras and M.Tech in Microwaves
        and Radar Engineering from IIT, Kharagpur. He joined IIT Madras, as Project Associate in 1980,
        and carried out research in Microwave Antenna Design and Near-field Measurement Techniques.
        He then obtained PhD in Antennae and Measurement Techniques from IIT, Madras. In the past,
        he has been the recipient of Best Defence Research and Development Organisation - Outstanding
        Scientist for 2012 award.</string>

    <string name="speaker2">Vilas Shinde is official spokesperson of Mumbai’s dabbawalas, the city’s
        famed tiffin delivery service. Started in 1890 by Mahadeo Havaji Bachche, the service has grown
        exponentially over the years. It started with a fleet of around a hundred men and has now become
        a full-fledged corporation. The dabbawalas operate with laser precision, misplacing the tiffins
        is a myth for them. They employ public transport like local trains and bicycles for deliveries
        and practise rigid adherence to a schedule. The system that they employ to keep a track of over
        2,00,000 lunch-boxes that are ferried every day is still a mystery to many. Mr. Shinde will
        step-by-step decode the clandestine ways of the dabbawalas and introduce you to the exciting
        world of this ingenious workforce!</string>

    <!-- For Tech Expo Activity -->
    <string name="Kalam">Keeping true to the phrase, ‘saving the best for the last’, we present to you the last exhibit of the Tech Expo- the Kalam SAT. Kalam SAT, which is named after the late Dr. APJ Abdul Kalam, is the brainchild of child prodigy Rifath Sharook who was only 18 years old when he made it with his high school team. It weighs a meagre 64 grams and is fitted in a 3.8 centimetres cube making it the lightest and smallest satellite in the world. Owing to its compactness, NASA launched the Kalam SAT on 22 June 2017 from Wallops Island flight facility in Virginia. The Kalam SAT is a shining example of India\’s scientific progress and it is our honour to have it at Abhiyantriki 2018.Keeping true to the phrase, ‘saving the best for the last’, we present to you the last exhibit of the Tech Expo- the Kalam SAT.</string>
    <string name="MiniHumanoidProject">The Mini Humanoid Robot is a marvel of modern day engineering. It stands 14" inches tall and consists of 16 servo motors working in tandem to mimic human movement. The Robot can easily dance, sing, and walk. It can also perform other activities which include yoga and swimming. Do not miss this once in a lifetime chance to catch the Mini Humanoid Robot in action only at Abhiyantriki 2018!</string>
    <string name="RoboticsLab">SP Robotics Maker Lab will demonstrate the working of Bluetooth controlled Pick and Place Robot, Pit Avoider Robot, Gesture-controlled Robot, Autonomous Walking Quadruped, and many more. SP Robotics Maker Lab will demonstrating IOT Enabled personal assistant that can speak with, remind, and help the user monitor devices and control them from anywhere around the world. Visit Abhiyantriki 2018 to witness these cutting edge innovations live!</string>
    <string name="R2D2">R2-D2 is inspired by its namesake astromech droid from Star Wars. The user can control the droid with a smart device or keep Artoo in top shape with olographic simulations. Visit Abhiyantriki 2018 to watch this iconic droid being brought to life like never before.</string>
    <string name="NetraPro">Netra Pro is the most versatile UAVs around! It can used in demanding conditions as it’s rugged &amp; IP53 ingress certified. It is also very versatile as it supports exotic payload combination such as simultaneous day and night cameras, LiDAR, multispectral cameras &amp; supply drops. Useful in Security &amp; Surveillance, Inspection, Photogrammetry, Traffic Management, Crowd Management, Disaster Relief, Harsh Environment, &amp; Operation Supply Drops. Catch it live only at Abhiyantriki 2018!</string>
    <string name="SPRK">The Sprk lighting lab allows anyone to program their robot. Owing to its size, the bot provides excellent accessibility. Drag and drop actions, controls, operators, &amp; move to give your bot the orders. Visit Abhiyantriki 2018 to watch it live!</string>
    <string name="A1Chek">The A1Chek is Smart HbA1C Meter used to quantitatively measure the concentration of HbA1C in whole blood, suitable for the self-monitoring of HbA1C for diabetes patients. It helps users to understand their diabetes, control status or to monitor their risk of developing diabetes making it an excellent diagnosis and management tool! Catch it in action at Abhiyantriki 2018!</string>
    <string name="TouchB">ToucHb is a non-invasive anaemia screening device which works by illuminating &amp; taking an image of the exposed conjunctiva of an individual with visible light. It then quantifies pallor to give a semiquantitative estimate of haemoglobin. ToucHb is intended for screening purpose in primary health settings and is not to be used for diagnostic or emergency application. To know more about this ingenious machine, visit Abhiyantriki 2018!</string>
    <string name="Nkd">Nkd POD+ is a bottle with built-in filter 585ML. It is a Tritan bottle with silicone finish that allows the user to drink healthy, clean, and safe water from taps, rivers, and lakes. The bottle energises the water by removing up to 99.9% of bacteria, viruses, parasites, and more. It slightly alkalises the water and increases antioxidant. To know more, visit the Tech Expo at Abhiyantriki 2018!</string>
    <string name="Neurosky">Neurosky is the 1st company to come out with a medical/research grade personal EEG headset with their own proprietary chip set TGAM. Puzzlebox Orbit is a kickstarter project by Steve Castellotti which was successfully commercialized as a Brain Computer Interface (BCI) product. Watch it live only at Abhiyantriki 2018!</string>
    <string name="Ugears">Ugears is the creator and manufacturer of unique self-propelled mechanical models sets designed for self-assembly without glue and made entirely of high-grade wooden material! Some models draw inspiration from real-life mechanisms, some are absolutely unique, and all of them have been designed by Ugears from scratch. Catch their exhibit live at Abhiyantriki 2018!</string>

    <!-- For Auto Expo Activity -->
    <string name="Bike">Zooming around the campus, we had an array of superbikes whose hums and roars left the audience awestruck.</string>
    <string name="Car">The vintage cars present at the expo helped students gain perspective about different cars, their specifications, and the enhancements in the technology involved.</string>
    <!--Other things-->
    <string name="title_text">Google Sign-In</string>

    <!-- Sign-in status messages -->
    <string name="signed_in_fmt1">SIGNED IN AS:\n</string>
    <string name="signed_in1">NAME:</string>
    <string name="signed_in_fmt2">EMAIL-ID:</string>

    <string name="signed_in">Signed in</string>
    <string name="signing_in">Signing in</string>
    <string name="signed_out">Signed out</string>
    <string name="signed_in_err">"Error: please check logs."</string>
    <string name="error_null_person">
        Error: Plus.PeopleApi.getCurrentPerson returned null. Ensure that the Google+ API is
        enabled for your project, you have a properly configured google-services.json file
        and that your device has an internet connection.
    </string>
    <string name="loading">Loading…</string>
    <string name="auth_code_fmt">Auth Code: %s</string>
    <string name="id_token_fmt">ID Token: %s</string>

    <!-- Google Play Services error for Toast -->
    <string name="play_services_error_fmt">Google Play Services Error: %i</string>

    <!-- Button labels -->
    <string name="sign_out">Sign Out</string>
    <string name="disconnect">Disconnect</string>
    <string name="refresh_token">Get Fresh Token</string>

    <!-- Content Description for images -->
    <string name="desc_google_icon">Google Logo</string>

    <!-- Rationale for asking for Contacts -->
    <string name="contacts_permission_rationale">Contacts access is needed in order to retrieve your email address.</string>

    <!-- Activity Names and Descriptions -->
    <string name="name_sign_in_activity">SignInActivity</string>
    <string name="desc_sign_in_activity">Signing in, signing out, and revoking access.</string>
    <string name="desc_sign_in_activity_scopes">Signing in, signing out, and revoking access with Google Drive permissions.</string>

    <string name="name_id_token_activity">IdTokenActivity</string>
    <string name="desc_id_token_activity">Retrieving an ID Token for the user.</string>

    <string name="desc_auth_code_activity">Demonstrate retrieving an auth code for authorizing your server.</string>
    <string name="name_auth_code_activity">ServerAuthCodeActivity</string>

    <string name="desc_rest_activity">Demonstrate using Google Sign In with a Google REST API</string>
    <string name="name_rest_activity">RestApiActivity</string>

    <!-- Messages for the Rest API activity -->
    <string name="connections_fmt">Connections: %1$s</string>
    <string name="msg_contacts_failed">Get contacts failed.</string>

    <!-- Server Client ID.  This should be a valid Web OAuth 2.0 Client ID obtained
         from https://console.developers.google.com/ -->
    <string name="server_client_id">YOUR_SERVER_CLIENT_ID</string>
</resources>
