<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Abhiyantriki</string>
    <string name="clg_name">K. J. Somaiya College of Engineering</string>
    <string name="Open">Opens navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="Close">Closes navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="kjsce">The K. J. Somaiya College of Engineering was established in 1983 at
        Somaiya, Vidyavihar. It offers 4-year bachelors degree courses in five diverse departments.
        KJSCE is an Autonomous college affiliated to the University of Mumbai and is recognized by
        the All India Council for Technical Education. The college hosts three huge festivals:
        Abhiyantriki, Skream, and Symphony</string>
    <string name="abhiyantriki">Abhiyantriki is the annual technical festival of K.J. Somaiya College
        of Engineering. Previously, organizations like DRDO, BARC, ISRO, DAE have participated in
        the fest along with prominent personalities such as the late Dr. A.P.J. Abdul Kalam, R
        Chidambaram, Abhas Mitra etc. It is a culmination of the brightest young minds coming in to
        compete in the various technical activities that take place during the two day long
        celebration.</string>
<string name="year_98">Abhiyantriki introduced as an individual, standalone festival of technical
    grandeur and pomp.</string>
    <string name="year_08">Funds collected this year were all donated for the rehabilitation of the
        flood struck Bihar and Abhiyantriki rose in popularity with extensive media coverage.</string>
    <string name="year_09">KJSCE marks 25 years since its inauguration, and the closing ceremony of
        Abhiyantriki was ornamented by the presence of late Dr. A.P.J. Abdul Kalam.</string>
    <string name="year_14">The maiden year for Start-up and Auto Expo, Abhiyantriki this year also
        encompassed Rohit Suri, the Jaguar India CEO as one of the keynote speakers.</string>
    <string name="year_16">Abhiyantriki extended by a day, now was a two-day long fest with its
        flagship event being a technical exhibition presided over by ISRO.</string>
    <string name="year_17">Attending to the likes of DRDO, DAE and BARC, Abhiyantriki garnered a
        running footfall of over 15,000 for the first time in its history!</string>
    <string name="pubg">The PUBG fever has infected everyone and with a game as addictive and
        intense as this, it’d be a shame for it to not be a part of Abhiyantriki ‘18. It’s time to
        loot all the crates in sight and face the terrors of Pochinki as you run away from the
        dreaded blue circle of death.</string>
    <string name="laser">Abhiyantriki is not all about fascinating gizmos. There’s something in the
        bag for everyone. Increase the fun quotient with Laser Tag only at KJSCE Abhiyantriki 2018.
        Come and engage in this challenging battle of lasers to get the experience of a lifetime.
    </string>
    <string name="drone">Do drones remind you of surveillance and all things boring? Take part in
        the drone racing event organised by Drona Aviation only at Abhiyantriki 2018 and that too
        at no cost!</string>
    <string name="meme">Memes have become a part and parcel of a student’s life. And for engineers,
        memes are a stress buster during exams. An early morning cup of tea with some amusing memes
        to go through makes one’s day lively. And Abhiyantriki 2018 has something exhilarating for
        all those meme fanatics out there. The best entries will win amazing prizes. Don’t miss this
        chance to show everyone who’s the greatest meme-lord of KJSCE.</string>
    <string name="fifa">Popularized as a part of the Indian pop culture because of the shenanigans by
        AIB in association with Shahrukh Khan, we present to you FIFA Manager. Be in charge of a team
        and pave its way towards victory. Have you got what it takes to manage a team and lead it to
        victory?</string>
    <string name="cs">From time immemorial, one thing that describes engineers the best would be the
        legendary FPS, Counter Strike. It’s time to Rush B and come out of your congested, damp and
        clammy hostel rooms and go guns blazing in a tournament to decide who has got the eagle eyed
        vision worthy of the Golden Glock.</string>
    <string name="CastleMath">With the lectures frying your brains to a crisp with the arrays of
        Epsilons and Gammas, it is time to bring math outside the classroom. With this exciting event
        presented by Team Emfinity, we hope all the zealots of math bring out their inner fangirl.
    </string>

</resources>
